http://www.engineready.com/privacy-policy/

Principles of Privacy – Site Visitors
The privacy of visitors to the EngineReady.com website is guaranteed as per the following privacy principles:
Principle 1 – No Collection of Personal Information
EngineReady.com does not collect involuntarily provided personal information such as name, age, phone number or address from visitors to ours or our clients’ websites. We do not combine anonymous traffic analysis information with any personal information such as name, age, phone number or mailing address. Our site’s server collects data in aggregate form only and data is not recorded or stored for individual visitors.
Principle 2 – Use of IP Addresses
Visitor IP addresses are recorded by every site on the internet. EngineReady.com collects this information as well, but does so exclusively for the following purposes: (1) collection of anonymous statistical data; (2) administration of our web site and servers; (3) improvement of our services.
Principle 3 – Use of Cookies
As is common practice, our web server stores cookies (logs of basic information) of visitors to our website. This is limited to IP address, browser type, the referring webpage, and the time of visit. We use this information to conduct anonymous traffic analysis. The information embedded in cookies does not include personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address. Most browsers are set by default to allow cookies. However, if you
Principles of Privacy – Clients
Principle 1 – Your Information is Confidential
All the statistical information we compile for your website is considered confidential. We do not disclose statistics about your website(s) to any third party without your consent. To ensure the privacy of your data, our servers are protected by the highest industry standard security technology: a firewall and security analyzers using SSL encryption to protect transmission of data.
Principle 2 – Limited Access to Your Information
EngineReady.com staff cannot access, modify, or otherwise divulge the statistical information we compile for your site except for the express purpose of generating reports which have been authorized by you or otherwise agreed to by you, or unless acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of EngineReady.com; (3) enforce the EngineReady.com Terms of Service; or (4) troubleshoot any service problems.
Principle 3 – No Site-Specific Data is Divulged to Any Third-Party
EngineReady.com compiles statistics across all our clients’ web sites in order to conduct our services. This information is compiled and stored only in an aggregate form, and in no event will we present specific site data without your permission to any third party.
Principle 4 – Personal Information
Registering for our services requires users to provide both contact information (such as name, e-mail, phone number), and billing information (such as credit card details). This personal and financial information is securely stored and is used only with the express consent of our clients for communication and billing for our products and services only
For More Information
If you have any questions or comments about our policies, services, or your experience with EngineReady.com, please contact us. We would love to hear from you.
Some of our Clients
Search our site
Search for:
Social
Want tips for being found on the web? Just read our blog
Engine Ready blog. Learn some tips and tricks from experts.
GO TO THE BLOG
Engine Ready, was the first to combine search engine optimization with website analytics. Engine Ready provides software and services to improve client’s online marketing results.
Questions?
